Guide to the Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
  - WMATA (Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority), 1996 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Northern Virginia Technology Council, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Consortium of Universities of the Washington Metropolitan Area, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - IT workforce gap, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Balanced Budget Act of 1997 (not foldered) (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Constituent mail (not foldered), 1997 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding immigration; H.R. 347, May-July 1997 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding healthcare; Military Health Services System, June-July 1997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - H.R. 2515 information, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Mt. Vernon Sierra Club Woodbridge Wild Life Refuge, June 1998 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - American Heritage Rivers, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - 106th Interstate Waste, January 1999 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Waste information, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Kyoto update, Buenos Aires, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Superfund info, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - EPA (Environmental Protection Agency) CRS (Congressional Research Service) info, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Larry Kline, Neabsco Creek, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Relocation of the Cape Hatteras lighthouse, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - CRS (Congressional Research Service) Clean Water Act, September 17, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Water destination research, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Propane regulations, September 1998 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Acid rain information, October 1998 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 1290 Information, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Animal damage control info (CRS), November 14, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Air Force Chimps, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - BLM (Bureau of Land Management) Adopt-A-Horse, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Whale Conservation Information, 1990-1997 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Crop Insurance, March 1999 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Terminator technology, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Energy Efficiency info, July 1998 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Earth Force Summit info, March 1999 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - H.R. 408, International Dolphin Program Conservation Act, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - CAMPFIRE (Communal Areas Management Programme for Indigenous Resources)(elephants), 1997 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Fur protest info, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Guidelines (proposed) for delisting of species under ESA (Endangered Species Act), 1998 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Circus information, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Sea turtles (not foldered), October 12, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Doris Day Animal League legislative briefing, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Anteon Corp / NVRP (Northern Virginia Regional Partnership) grant request info, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Chesapeake Bay info, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - General environmental articles, November 1998 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Gas station storage tanks EPA (Environmental Protection Agency) enforcement, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Dog fur information, December 15, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - USDA (U.S. Department of Agriculture) class action discrimination, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Federal government recycling policies, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Blacklisting, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Sikh Mosque, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Carlow International, May-June 1999 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Teligent, rooftop access, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - WW (Woodrow Wilson) Bridge, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - AAAV (Advanced Amphibious Assault Vehicle), 1999 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Transportation Bill, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - AOL (America Online), Time Warner, January 2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Year 2000 Problem, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Appropriations Subcommittee on VA, HUD and Independent Agencies (not foldered), April 14, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Ronald Reagan Airport, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Community outreach, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Grant management reform, March 1998 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - One Call legislature, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Caldwell Corporation, D.C., September 1997 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - HHS (Department of Health and Human Services), Diversity contracting, Nancy-Ann Min DeParle, October 1997 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, March-July 1995 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, 1995-1997 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding the Clean Air Act (not foldered), June-August 1997 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Three magazines: Retired Officer Magazine (November 1998), Playback (July/August 1998), Code One Lockheed Martin (October 1998) (not foldered) (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Constituent cards regarding Medicare; Environmental Defense (not foldered), Circa 1998 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail regarding multiple issues (not foldered), August-September 2000 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail regarding multiple issues, July-August 9, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail regarding multiple issues, July 26-31, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail regarding multiple issues, August 15-24, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Nixon Library (letter), December 1, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Katrina slides (transparencies), 2006 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - The Contract with America (transparencies), 1994 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - SS (Social Security) and budget slides (transparencies), 2005 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - DRC (?) newsletter, franked mail, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, palm card, Fall 2003 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - 2004 January newsletter, sent out December 2003 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - December / January newsletter, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Franked mail, July 2004 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - In box - Michael Hettinger 8:00pm transparency, Circa 1995 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Town Hall slide presentation, Winter 2004 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 22, Postal Accountability and Enhancement Act, July 26, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - GROC (Committee on Government Reform and Oversight) Organizational Meeting, February 9, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Pilot Age 65, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Potomac Bridge, April 9, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Norfolk Harbor, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Occoquan Bridge, October 6, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Norfolk Souther / I-81, July 2006 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Smarttrip FTA (Federal Transit Administration) letter, July 12, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Linton Hall Road, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - 66 Inside Beltway CTB (Commonwealth Transportation Board) letter, March 9, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Metro T-LU, February 3, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Minimum guarantee T-3, March 2004 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - HOT (High Occupancy Toll) lanes, September 2007 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Hybrids, December 4, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - I-66 HOT (High Occupancy Toll) lanes, January 2005 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Prince William / Linton Hall, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - United pension, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - United Airlines, 2002-2003 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Battlefield bypass, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Dunn Loring 495, December 2004 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Rail, 107th, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Metro, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Passenger Reaccommodation, February 3, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Transportation, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Amtrak, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - H.R. 2015, Balanced Budget Act of 1997, June 24, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July-August 1997 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 11-14, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence; issue files; recommendation letters, 1995-1997 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence; 1996 NRCC (National Republican Congressional Committee)Democrat Attack Themes, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Census 2000 Information for Congress, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Census, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - CSA (Contract Services Association) of America, H.R. 716 & S 314, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - TRSA (Textile Rental Services Association of America), 1998 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Debt collection Improvement Act (blue folder), 1998 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Census 2000 Information (blue folder), 1998 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Census 2000 dress rehearsal mid-term status report, September 1998 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Larry Doby (not foldered), July 10, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Howard T. McIntyre, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Kids in Trouble, attn: John Hishta, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Catherine Filene Shouse, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Nelson Mandela Gold Medal, May 5, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - H. Con. Res. 229, Submarine Stamp, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - VFW (Veterans of Foreign Wars) stamp, March 1998 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - WWII Memorial, June 1997 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - George Washington sense of Congress (postage stamp), March 1998 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Irish Potato Famine Resolution, September-December 1997 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Masters Swimming Commemorative Stamp Act, September 1997 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Frank Sinatra Gold Medal H.R. 279, February-May 1997 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Eugene Betit, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - 2000 Census, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous constituent mail; Privatization; Financial management, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Davos briefing booklet (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Davos briefing booklet (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Illegal Gun Task Force Hearing, April 2008 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - DoJ (Department of Justice) Tax Division, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Oklahoma City, GSA event, April 1996 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Virginia, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - In manila envelope - Peter Sirh, FEC (Federal Election Commission), October-November 1996 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - FY (Fiscal Year), 1995 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Budget FY (Fiscal Year), 1996 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - NRCC Republican Conference presentation (not foldered), March 7, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Legal reform, March 1996 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Congrats, thanks to TMD (Thomas M. Davis), 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Internal Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper files (1 of 2), 1994-1998 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper files (2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Report 104-196 for H.R. 2076 (not foldered), August 2, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Letters of recommendation, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, September-October 1997 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Congressional Record of the 105th congress, No. 98, 99, 101 (not foldered), July 11-16, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and letters of recommendation, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Medicare conference report, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Medicare (includes CD with PDF Medicare brochure), 2004 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Second Medicare, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Medicare Part D, franked mail, Circa 2005 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Medicare Part D, November-December 2005 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - NTIS (National Technical Information Service), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Security of Federal Buildings, April 28, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Subcommittee on Human Resources, February 6-7, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Waste and Fraud, May 17, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Accountable Congress, May 25, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - CFC (Combined Federal Campaign), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Firefighters, March 21-22, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 1561 (not foldered), May 3, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - IRS (Internal Revenue Service) (blue folder), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 461, January 9, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Cordant, Inc., August 11, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Subcommittee on government management, information, and technology, January-February 1995 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - VOA (Voice of America), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Retirement Protection Act, GATT (General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - GATT (General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Hearing on Consolidating Federal Programs and Organizations (blue folder), May 23, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Hearing on Strengthening Departmental Management Within the Federal Government (blue folder), May 1995 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - GMIT (Government Management, Information and Technology) hearing (dark blue folder), May 11-16, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Performance Measurement, Benchmarking, and Reengineering (dark blue folder), June 20, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Regulatory Transition Act of 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Regulatory Transition Act (mark-up), January-February 1995 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Clean Air Flexibility Act of 1995, January 1995 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - ACDA (Arms Control and Disarmament Agency), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - GMIT (Government Management, Information and Technology), Department of Energy (dark blue folder), May 1995 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - C.Q. (Congressional Quarterly) information, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - CRS (Congressional Research Service) products and information, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - GMIT (Government Management, Information and Technology), Hearing on The National Performance Review (dark blue folder), May 1995 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - GMIT (Government Management, Information and Technology), GSA panel (dark blue folder), March 1995 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - H.R. 719 (value engineering); H.R. 1561, January-June 1995 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - GAO (Government Accountability Office) report: Military bases (1 of 2), July 2005 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - GAO (Government Accountability Office) report: Military bases (2 of 2), July 2005 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Metro briefing book (1 of 2), July 2005 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Metro briefing book (2 of 2), July 2005 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Medicare Prescription Drug, Improvement, and Modernization Act of 2003 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Medicare Prescription Drug, Improvement, and Modernization Act of 2003 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Battling bioterrorism (Hearing), December 14, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Woodrow Wilson Bridge improvement (dark blue folder), September 1995 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Thank you letters to Davis, April-August 1995 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Neabsco (river), March-April 1997 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Buyer's Choice, DMA (Direct Marketing Association), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Postal, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Washington Aqueduct, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Chip Nottingham, Handicapped parking issue, 1994-1997 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Alaska ANWR 1002 Area, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Landmines, April 1997 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - FCC (Federal Communications Commission), March 1997 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Jay Khim, April-May 1997 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - VA HUD, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Modular Design System (MDS), April 1997 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Employee benefits; Highsmith Appeal Bond, October 1996-1997 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding NCUA (National Credit Union Administration), January 14-24, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Washington Aqueduct, 1996-1997 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Washington Aqueduct, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Washington Aqueduct, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Davis articles, 1991-1994 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Davis articles, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, January 1997, October 1997 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - District of Columbia Economic Recovery Act (dark blue folder), April 15, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Lorton letters (?); H.R. 2546; FEHB (Federal Employee Health Benefits), 1995 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Ex-files, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - USGS (U.S. Geological Survey), RiFs (Reduction in Force), 1995 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Paperwork Reduction Act, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Pyrocap; Odor-Go, March-May 1996 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Federal Acquisition Reform Act of 1995 (not foldered), July 27, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Federal Acquisition Reform Act of 1995 (not foldered), July 27, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Federal Acquisition Streamlining Act of 1994 (not foldered), October 13, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Patent-trademark (GATT (General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade)), February 1995 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 3525 Church arson. (includes diskette), June-July 1996 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous: CRS reports; Statements by Davis; Correspondence; articles, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Reserves policy, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Postal reform, June 24, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - NASA, 1999-2002 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Patriot Act, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Edward F. Lawton, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Mainland Affairs Council (Taiwan), 2002 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Taiwan, Brian Stout (includes tourism CD), 2002 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - FOP (Fraternal Order of Police), February 2003 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Michigan Lawsuit, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - LST (Landing Ship Tanks), 2002 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Ergonomics, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Federal Minimum Wage, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Drug Policy, February 12, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Columbia Tragedy (NASA), 2003 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Drug Free Schools, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Homeland Security, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Iraq, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Military Housing, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - H.R. 4546 (dark blue folder), 2002 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - FY 2003 Budget Resolution, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Homeland Security, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Arming Pilots, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - First Responders Special Trust Act of 2003: First Act (summary), 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Domestic intelligence gap, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Federal retirees, H.R. 583, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Lorton Correctional Complex, Lorton, VA, GSA Report to Congress, January 3, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Military Retiree HC (Health Care) (report), June 2003 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Civil Rights Tax Act, March-April 2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Marine Corps Heritage, 2000-2003 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - USS Liberty (research and constituent mail), 2002 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Military draft, Universal Service Act, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Military absentee voting, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Intelligence authorization, May-June 2003 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - EPG (Engineering Proving Ground), VDOT (Virginia Department of Transportation), June 2003 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - State budgets, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Veterans Issues, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - School of America, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - World War II Memorial, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Resolution on the Budget FY 2004, March 2003 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Concurrent Receipt (Prohibition on Concurrent Receipt Military Retired Pay and Veterans' Disability Compensation), 2002 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - FSC (Foreign Sales Corporation) / ETI (Extraterritorial Income). (CRS reports), 2003 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - NIH (National Institutes of Health)primate experiments. (Brian Stout), 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Employee stock ownership, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Iraq WMD (Weapons of Mass Destruction), 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - H.R. 2038 (Assault Weapons Ban), May 2003 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Federal Prison Industries (Brian Stout), 2003 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Hurricane Isabel, September-December 2003 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - H.R. 3518, Telecommuting Choice Act, January 2000 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Export Controls letter, June 2000 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Lists, correspondence, etc. on Export Controls, February-May 2000 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Export Controls correspondence, March, May 2000 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Export Controls readings and news clips, February-May 2000 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Export Controls signature confirmation, February-May 2000 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Export Controls, Dear Colleague, February 2000 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Networked Economy Summit, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - IIT event (iit2005: technology without borders), 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Networked Economy Summit, June 9-11, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - H.R. 4454, 108th, May 20, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - H.R. 1532, Animal Fighting, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 1563, Antifreeze Safety, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Random, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - National Zoo, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Poultry exports, February-March 2003 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - H.R. 3446, Yellowstone Buffalo, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Dear Colleagues, TMD (Thomas M. Davis) signed, May 2007 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Environment, VA air pollution briefs, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Co-sponsored, 107th, June 2002 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Local environment groups, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Chesapeake Bay Program, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Chesapeake Bay review of the Water Quality Model (not foldered), Undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Chesapeake Bay, 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Fannie Mae, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - World Com, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Stock Options Freedom Act, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Social Security, 107th, H.R. 2, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - H.R. 10, Pension reform, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Pensions reform. H.R. 1102, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Uptick Rule, April, June 2008 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Foreclosure Prevention Act, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - GSE (Government sponsored enterprise), 2005 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Mortgage Reform Anti Predatory Lending, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Home Owners Defense Act, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Stimulus, January 2008 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Treasury Overhaul Plan, April 2008 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Affordable Housing Trust Fund, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Flood-Insurance Modernization Act, September 2007 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Terrorism Risk Insurance, September 2007 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - National Affordable Housing Trust Fund Act, August-September 2007 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Anti Predatory Lending and Mortgage Reform Act. H.R. 3915, November 2007 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Expanding Homeownership, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - FASB (Financial Accounting Standards Board) Letter, January 30, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - FASB (Financial Accounting Standards Board) Letter re: stock options, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - OCC (Office of the Comptroller of the Currency) preemption, May, July 2004 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Stock Option Acting Reform Act, H.R. 3574, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - H.R. 2622 (Fair and Accurate Credit Transactions Act), September 2003 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - H.R. 1474, Check clearing for 21st Century, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - H.R. 3579, Credit Union Regulatory Improvement Act, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Broadband reports / studies, February 2001 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Building Access, Circa 2000 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Broadband Internet Access Act, 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Voting scorecards, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Broadband Internet Access Act, 2001-2002 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Broadband news articles, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Gov't (government) mgmt (management) Y2K report cards, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Y2K, October 27, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Newsletter with photographs (prints and negatives), August 1996 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - H.R. 1542, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Telecom industry position papers, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Telephone service, May, July 2001 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Telephone charges (CRS report), November 6, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Cable, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 6)